(Howard:)My mom's been
kind of an emotional wreck...
(Howard:)...since that dentist she was dating
dumped her.
(Raj:)Dumped her? What did he use, a forklift?
(Raj:)Sorry.
(Raj:)There's nothing funny
about morbid obesity.
(Howard:)She's huge, it was funny.
(Howard:)Anyway, I was just hoping that maybe you
could check in on her tomorrow night...
(Howard:)...make sure she's doing okay.
- Dude, I'm a single man.
(Raj:)Saturday night is my party night.
Really, what do you got going on?
(Raj:)I don't know, maybe drive
down to Hollywood...
(Raj:)...hit a few hot spots,
see if I can get lucky.
Tell me if this sounds familiar. Ahem.
You pay $15 to park,
you stand on the sidewalk for an hour...
(Howard:)...until you break down and
give the bouncer 20 to let you in.
(Howard:)You push your way to the bar
where you drink an $18 cosmopolitan.
(Howard:)Then you stare at a pretty girl
and imagine your perfect life together.
(Howard:)Children, grandchildren.
Meanwhile, she leaves with a guy...